♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 5=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 5 =
How was it? I got the job done, right?
كيف وجدته؟  لقد أنجزت العمل ، أليس كذلك؟
I did what you asked.
فعلت ما طلبته.
You have to help our comic company.
عليك أن تساعد شركتنا المصورة.
You have to keep your promise.
عليك أن تفي بوعدك.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
My liver hurts.
كبدي يؤلمني.
That's not where your liver is, sir.
هذا ليس مكان كبدك يا ​​سيدي.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Yun Xiangxiang. Very poetic, isn't it?
يون شيانغشيانغ.  شاعرية جدا ، أليس كذلك؟
Miss Yun.
ملكة جمال يون.
Do you know how many years in prison awaits you
هل تعرف عدد السنوات التي تنتظرك في السجن
for trespassing?
للتعدي على ممتلكات الغير؟
What?
ماذا؟
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
But I'll let it pass
لكنني سأتركها تمر
since you helped me just now.
منذ أن ساعدتني الآن.
So,
لذا،
you agreed to withdraw your appeal?
هل وافقت على سحب الاستئناف الخاص بك؟
That's another matter.
هذه مسألة أخرى.
Chu He.
تشو هي.
Don't let me see your face ever again.
لا تدعني أرى وجهك مرة أخرى.
Otherwise you'll really have a chat with the police.
وإلا ستجري محادثة مع الشرطة.
Fu Sihan, you liar!
فو سيهان ، أنت كاذب!
You bad man! Crook!
أنت رجل سيء!  المحتال!
You are a fraud!
أنت محتال!
Grandpa.
الجد.
Sihan.
سيهان.
Do you have anything else to say?
هل لديك أي شيء آخر لتقوله؟
This is a misunderstanding.
هذا سوء فهم.
Misunderstanding? No way!
سوء فهم؟  مستحيل!
I saw her on your bed with my own eyes!
رأيتها على سريرك بأم عيني!
Shut up!
اسكت!
This is not how you act as an elder!
هذه ليست الطريقة التي تتصرف بها كشيخ!
Sit down!
اجلس!
Sihan.
سيهان.
Keep going.
واصل التقدم.
She is not pregnant.
هي ليست حامل.
On that day,
في ذلك اليوم،
she was just feeling ill.
كانت فقط تشعر بالمرض.
You are the biggest grandson in the family.
أنت أكبر حفيد في الأسرة.
You have to always remember who you are.
عليك أن تتذكر دائما من أنت.
And be careful with what you do.
وكن حذرًا فيما تفعله.
Yes.
نعم.
Not every girl is entitled
لا يحق لكل فتاة
to be the wife of the biggest grandson in our family.
أن تكون زوجة أكبر حفيد في عائلتنا.
What's her background?
ما هي خلفيتها؟
I want to meet her.
اريد ان اقابلها
Grandpa.
الجد.
We just started dating not long ago.
لقد بدأنا للتو المواعدة منذ وقت ليس ببعيد.
Perhaps...
ربما...
After some more time...
بعد بعض الوقت ...
She's not just a random stranger you met, is she?
إنها ليست مجرد غريب عشوائي قابلته ، أليس كذلك؟
She's not a random stranger.
إنها ليست غريبة بشكل عشوائي.
She's...
إنها ...
She's the daughter of the Yun Group.
إنها ابنة مجموعة يون.
Yun Group?
مجموعة يون؟
The Yun Group has always been abroad.
لطالما كانت مجموعة Yun في الخارج.
I've only heard of them,
لقد سمعت عنهم فقط ،
but never had the chance to get closer.
ولكن لم تتح لها الفرصة للاقتراب.
I still think Zhirou is a better choice.
ما زلت أعتقد أن Zhirou هو خيار أفضل.
Gentle, intelligent, virtuous.
رقيق ، ذكي ، فاضل.
And a big star.
ونجم كبير.
Her dad has worked for our group for years.
عمل والدها في مجموعتنا لسنوات.
He's very loyal to our group.
إنه مخلص جدًا لمجموعتنا.
To our group,
لمجموعتنا ،
or to you?
او لك
Watch your mouth.
انتبه لكلامك.
Yes.
نعم.
Well then,
حسنا اذن،
just bring that girl here
فقط أحضر تلك الفتاة هنا
to see me.
لرؤيتي.
No?
رقم؟
Of course, grandpa.
بالطبع يا جدي.
Sihan.
سيهان.
At the shareholders' meeting today,
في اجتماع المساهمين اليوم ،
I have announced to everyone
لقد أعلنت للجميع
that I'll decide who will be the successor of this family
أنني سأقرر من سيكون خليفة هذه العائلة
in three months.
في غضون ثلاثة أشهر.
I hope you can make every move
آمل أن تتمكن من القيام بكل خطوة
with acumen and discretion.
بحكمة وتقدير.
Do not make grandpa
لا تجعل الجد
disappointed in you.
خاب ظني فيك.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
You are here.
أنت هنا.
Yeah.
نعم.
So miserable...
بائسة جدا ...
Mom!
أم!
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Did your doctor say anything?
هل قال طبيبك أي شيء؟
Is your condition getting worse?
هل تسوء حالتك؟
Don't be scared, mom.
لا تخافي يا أمي.
I'll be with you no matter what happens.
سأكون معك مهما حدث.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Such a miserable life for the heroine.
هذه حياة بائسة للبطلة.
Mom, can you stop being so childish?
أمي ، هل يمكنك التوقف عن أن تكون طفوليًا جدًا؟
Don't watch those crappy, childish, no-good-at-all romance dramas.
لا تشاهد تلك الدراما الرومانسية الجنونية ، الطفولية ، غير الجيدة على الإطلاق.
Why don't you read my comics?
لماذا لا تقرأ رسوم كاريكاتورية؟
Your melodrama comic
الكوميديا ​​الميلودرامية الخاصة بك
is so unreal.
غير واقعي جدا.
You need to find a boyfriend
أنت بحاجة إلى إيجاد صديق
and have some real life experience.
ولديك بعض الخبرة الواقعية.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Here.
هنا.
One more sip.
رشفة واحدة أخرى.
What's in the soup? It tastes funny.
ماذا يوجد في الحساء؟  طعمها مضحك.
What did you put in there?
ماذا وضعت هناك؟
This is the best soup you'll ever get to taste.
هذا هو أفضل حساء ستتذوقه على الإطلاق.
Here we have the creatures
هنا لدينا المخلوقات
up in the sky, down on the earth, and deep in the ocean.
في السماء ، على الأرض ، وفي أعماق المحيط.
I got all of them in this one pot.
لقد حصلت عليهم جميعًا في هذا القدر الواحد.
And they are?
و هم؟
Chicken, pork, and turtle.
الدجاج ولحم الخنزير والسلحفاة.
Go get married and learn to cook.
اذهب وتزوج وتعلم الطبخ.
This is a nightmare.
هذا هو كابوس.
You...
أنت...
Mom, I put a lot of efforts into this.
أمي ، لقد بذلت الكثير من الجهود في هذا.
Another sip.
رشفة أخرى.
Come on.
هيا.
Do it for me.
افعل ذلك من أجلي.
What happened to him?
ماذا حدث له؟
He jumped out of the building.
قفز من المبنى.
He should be in the orthopedics department nearby.
يجب أن يكون في قسم جراحة العظام القريب.
We'll just leave him here for a minute
سنتركه هنا لمدة دقيقة
until we get a bed for him.
حتى نحصل على سرير له.
What are you looking at?
الى ماذا تنظرين؟
You...
أنت...
Miss Yun.
ملكة جمال يون.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
He's...
إنه ...